♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Looney Tunes Edition.
Okay, Chef Fudd, I was a little
disappointed in you this week.
Your dish was
just a live rabbit
who thought
he was taking a bath.
But I used
carrots and celery.
Yes. I saw he was scrubbing his
back with a long celery stalk.
Chef Sylvester,
on the other hand,
I'm happy to say
your sufferin' succotash
was absolutely delicious.
Thanks.
Hello?
Oh, hi, Bonnie.
No, I'm not doing anything.
Just sitting here
with the baby.
Yeah, screw you, too.
Oh, hey, Bri.
Hey, you want to go out
and get some
gluten-free pizza?
I'm gluten-free now.
But, you know,
I'm not gonna be
annoying about it.
Too late.
Oh, we should be
gluten-free together!
Let's go to Whole Foods
and buy a bunch of stuff
from that weird aisle
nobody else goes down.
I can't. I got plans.
I'll see you later.
Oh, sure.
Maybe another time.
Ugh. I didn't seem
too desperate, right?
Don't answer. It's just that
Brian's been so distant lately,
and we used to be inseparable--
like Jack and Jill.
Oh, so then Jack takes
these two pails of water
and trips and totally
falls down the hill.
Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah. Hey,
I got a funny story.
Jill had a tooth fall out,
and she swallowed it,
and then we had to root
through her feces to find it.
And we did. And then
we took it to the dentist,
and he put it back
in her mouth.
So I guess
we're both klutzes, huh?
Why don't you spin
another tale, crap-tooth?
No? My turn again?
Okay. Jill's barren.
Good afternoon.
I'm Tom Tucker.
Some sad news this morning
as 38 schoolchildren drowned
when their--
excuse me-- when their
school bus hit a patch of ice
and drove off a loc--
what is wrong with me today?--
and drove off a local bridge.
And now the viral video
of the week,
with over seven million views.
For those of you
who loved "Screaming Sheep,"
we've got "Opera Penguin."
♪ La, ah, ah, ah. ♪
Is... is that it?
Is he gonna do it again? No?
Okay, so just
normal penguin stuff now.
Okay, cut back to me.
Uh, y-you can't?
The button broke off?
All right, well, a U.S. convoy
was ambushed in Kabul
this morning, so now
we're going to have a moment
of silence in remembrance...
♪ La... ♪
Oh, he does do it again.
That could be my favorite
thing I ever seen.
What is a penguin?
Is it some kind of bug?
What? You serious?
So it is a bug?
Hey, you know, that's
what we ought to do.
We ought to make
a viral video.
All right! Awesome!
Let's do it!
Oh, wait, I don't know if
you're gonna be in it, Joe.
I thought, while we filmed,
we'd just keep all of
our stuff on your lap.
What the hell
are you doing?
I saw a scary boy doing this,
and I thought I'd try it.
All right, have fun.
I'm late.
Late?
But I thought you and I
could hang out
and maybe watch Lois
shush Peter
while they watch Nashville.
Maybe another
time, Stewie.
There he goes again.
He's being so standoffish.
I don't understand.
Oh, we used to be that happy.
Wait a minute--
Joe and Bonnie
never used
to spend time together
until they had Susie.
Having a baby seems
to have made them closer.
Babies save relationships!
Oh, look at you--
you're flyin'!
Okay, thanks, Bonnie.
Next I want
to ride a bike.
That's it, Rupert!
That's how Brian and I
are going to improve
our relationship.
We're going to have a baby!
I say, this is my best idea
since I robbed
a Joseph A. Bank.
Three suits for 99 bucks?!
Take me to jail!
All right,
I want tonight to be perfect.
I'm gonna lay it all out
for Brian
why we should have
a baby together.
I don't know, I haven't
even thought about that.
Why are you so obsessed
with circumcision?
Oh, hey, look, you made
a little dinner party.
Hi, Rupert.
He won't be joining us.
Get up!
Please, sit.
You, uh... you okay?
I'm terrific. And that is
so sweet of you to ask.
You really are a natural
caregiver, aren't you?
Mm. Mm.
Do you mind not texting?
Sorry, sorry.
Just finishing right now.
Almost done.
There, all finished
riiiight...
now.
Thhhhere.
Thanks. So, I wanted
to talk to you about...
A-Are you just gonna
leave it on the table?
I-I won't look at it.
Great. So, I wanted to...
You're looking at it.
Sorry. Work.
It's not work.
It'll just take a second.
I-I normally wouldn't do this,
but I was already kind of
in the middle of something,
and I just need
to quickly respond,
and there I am
finiiished.
Ah, yeah.
Okay, just
a few more worrrds...
annnd...
d-done.
Sorry.
Okay, so...
Nah, nah, I'm
not gonna get it.
Then maybe we can
take it off the table.
No, no, just keep going.
I was thinking,
we should talk
about having a...
This isn't fun for me,
watching you text.
No, no, this is great.
Mm, mm, mm. Yum.
But I-I got to go.
I have a date.
This is serious, Rupert.
I'm losing him.
If we're going to fix
this relationship,
we need a baby
and we need it now.
I'm just going to take
a little bit of his DNA,
and soon we'll be proud parents,
like Ron Livingston's parents.
You know,
our son's a famous actor.
Really?
What's his name?
Oh, um...
he's, uh...
he was, like, the main guy
in Office Space.
Yeah. What else?
Uh... he has dark hair...
I don't know,
was he in Black Hawk Down?
Uh, he was in, like, at least
five Sex "in" the Citys.
What is his name?
Is your son
Ron Livingston?
Yes!
Oh, God! Thank God!
Ron Livingston!
Thank you!
That has been bugging me
all day.
Okay, let's see.
Now, what are the ingredients
to a viral Internet video?
Cats.
Yes, cats. Good.
Uh, uh, people reacting
to watching gross stuff.
Oh, yeah, 'cause they're like,
"Rah! That's gross!
Can I get a soda?
What? No.
Th-This is, like, the worst time
to ask for a soda.
Unbelievable.
You know what, we should
just go out and start filming.
'Cause I think we're
really gonna surprise everyone.
Like Buster Keaton did
in his first talking picture.
♪
♪Here we go.
I'm moving through the scene
and I slam the door.
Oh, no!
I slammed it too hard,
and the house
is gonna squash me!
Oh, it turned out
that window was there.
Pause for laugh and amazement.
All right, Rupert,
the fertilization device
is complete.
This will impregnate me
with the child
that will bring Brian and me
back together!
First, I add
Brian's hair and saliva,
and some preschool applications,
because we are
already way behind.
There. Now I just have
to get into the machine,
and then the machine does
whatever it has to do to me
in order to successfully
impregnate me.
We do not judge the machine.
We do not judge Stewie.
Good-bye, body.
You're gonna watch me
get pregnant.
I want to look at you
when it happens.
Yeah, you watch me,
bitch.
Good morning, Brian.
What is that?
I smell pee.
Yes, you do, Brian.
Oh, my God, that
thing's positive!
Is Lois pregnant again?
No...
Meg is pregnant?
You're getting warmer.
Wha... What have you done?
I think you mean,
what have we done?
What?!
Brian... we're pregnant!
Oh, my God!
And in 18 years,
he's going
to move away!
You're pregnant
with our baby?!
How could this
even happen?!
Simple. I took your DNA
and inserted it
into my temporary uterus
through my fertilization device.
Oh, my God,
you're serious!
People are gonna think I
had sex with a male baby
and then got him pregnant!
Oh, thank you for finding a way
to make it sound horrible.
We can't have
a baby, Stewie!
Is this about money?
Because I have a bit saved.
We could even use
my old crib.
You use your old crib!
Oh, right.
Stewie, you have
to get rid of it.
"Get rid of it"? You know,
why don't you just say it?
Say the word, Brian.
I want to hear you say it.
Abortion! Abortion!
You need to get a big fat
abortion right this second!
You can't even say it.
I think I'm
gonna throw up.
Oh, save the cheap theatrics.
This isn't one of your
crappy short stories.
This is real life,
mister, so man up!
You are getting an
abortion, Stewie.
I will not! Our child
is growing inside me!
Stop talking like that!
A-And how do you
even know it's mine?
How dare you!
So I'm just some slut?!
Well, this slut
is having your baby!
Why would you
even do this?
I thought
you'd be happy.
I mean, you have
all these amazing qualities,
and I'm kind of
good-looking.
I mean,
I'm no model, but...
Well, certainly
not a runway model.
I'd-I'd be more
catalogue, probably.
You know what?
Why not a runway model?
Why not? Why am I
always apologizing
for how good-looking I am?
I'm sick of it.
I can model in Paris.
We could take the baby with us.
We could be that kind of family.
What do you think?
Is it dead?
You hit me!
What kind of monster
hits a pregnant toddler!
If you ever lay a finger on me again,
I'll burn you in your bed.
Could... could you
do that now, please?
All right, Peter,
get the camera ready.
I got a viral
Internet video
that's gonna go straight
to the top of the charts.
Hi, I'm Joe Swanson,
and this is 30 impressions
in 30 seconds.
"Show me the money."
"Oh, behave."
"Good morning, Vietnam."
"Wait until they get a load
of me," said the Joker.
Some of these I'm paraphrasing.
Hey, I need you to
take me to the doctor
for my prenatal
vitamins.
I'm not taking you anywhere.
Geez, how far along are you?
I'm not really sure.
Two days, six months...
there's a certain amount of
guesswork involved in this.
Oh, and while I'm pregnant,
I'm going to need you
to change the cat litter.
We don't have a cat.
Ugh. Please don't
fight me on this.
Oh, my back is killing me.
And I've also been
experiencing a little...
morning sickness.
It's for the baby,
it's for the baby.
You look ridiculous
like that.
Not too ridiculous for you
to put a baby in me.
Okay, Raylene,
I'm Dr. Hartman.
Now, before we begin,
I want you to know
the record is just
past my watch.
Well, it takes two people
to break a record.
You look a little young.
How old are you?
Uh, 13? 14?
15. B-But he didn't force
himself on me.
I wanted it, too.
Well, that's
the important thing.
That's odd.
Your vagina seems to have
a penis and two testicles.
Oh, right. I, uh...
sneezed real hard
and all that came out.
Ah, that explains it.
Could you do that thing
where you take some fluid
and tell me if it's going
to be an imbecile or a cretin?
Oh, not to worry,
there are places
where those people
can be warehoused.
But from strictly
eyeballing you,
I'd say everything
looks fine.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Now, Brian, did you have
any questions for the doctor?
Yeah. Are there a lot of
stairs in this building?
God, we need so much stuff.
Look at how tiny all these
clothes are. It's so adorable.
I mean, what kind of feet
can fit into these shoes?
Your feet!
That's getting old, you know.
You better get on
board with this.
Aw, how far along are you?
Eight months.
You look amazing.
Let me ask you, are you leaking?
Because I've been leaking.
How old are you?
You look like you're 40,
which means whatever you've got
in there is 100% brain-damaged.
All right,
you have a good day.
I hated that lady.
I like these.
These are good. Very classy.
This feels
incredibly wrong.
Oh, we're going to want these,
Brian, believe me.
You can't see
my nipples, can you?
They're getting really large,
and I'm not sure
if I'm completely covering them.
Eh, you know what?
We'll see what we see.
Let's get a few candids.
Dad, can I get one of your head
on the belly?
Oh, "Dad."
I just got emotional.
♪ Having my baby ♪
♪ I'm a woman in love ♪
♪ And I love
what's goin' through me ♪
♪ Having my baby ♪
♪ It's another way
of sayin' how much I love you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Having my baby ♪
Okay, now people really love
that viral video
of a monkey forcin' that sex act
on a frog at the zoo.
So maybe we can find another
frog for somethin' like that.
You mean like that frog?
Who?
That frog in
the miniskirt
putting a quarter
in the jukebox.
♪ Shot through the heart ♪
♪ And you're to blame ♪
♪ You give love a bad name ♪
♪ Bad name ♪
♪ I play my part ♪
♪ And you play your game ♪
Bingo.
♪ You give love a bad name ♪
♪ Bad name ♪
♪ You give love... ♪
I'm concerned that frog's in
more trouble than she realizes.
I'm having such a craving
for burgers.
It's like my body is
just craving red meat.
And mint chip ice cream.
But only mint chip.
Any other ice cream
makes me want to puke.
Isn't that weird?
Yes, Stewie,
that's the one weird thing
in all this.
What are you looking at?
Go push your buttons.
My husband'll kick your ass.
Stop saying
I'm your husband.
Brian, I need you to
take me to the hospital.
Why?
My water just broke.
Oh, my God!
It's okay. Don't panic.
Call the doula.
Brian, you've got
to call the doula!
Doula? I-I don't
even know what that is!
It's a divorced woman who
knows about lady parts
and cheers you on.
Let's go!
You're gonna have
to drive a little faster!
I'm already going
over the speed limit.
Too late! Pull over!
It's starting to come out!
Of where?
I'm not sure exactly.
Brian, I'm going to need you
to deliver the baby.
Uh, uh, o-okay, c-can you wait a
second while I put a towel down?
I don't want anything
to get on the seats.
Oh, no, of course.
Our first priority should be
to keep the vinyl clean.
Oh, God. Oh, God,
it's coming! Oh...
Can you see the head?
I don't know
where to look!
Well, maybe you should look
at the part of me
where there's
a baby coming out!
How did Murphy Brown
make this look so easy?!
Careful, don't get
anything on the...
...seats.
Oh, God,
I think another one's coming!
I don't see it!
I think
it's coming out of my mouth!
There's more!
And they're coming out
of everywhere!
Ah! Kill me!
This hurts too much!
Holy!
What is happening?!
I don't know!
Brian, save the placenta.
Do you even have a placenta?
Well, whatever comes
out, save it. I want to eat it.
Oh, God,
they're crawling all over me!
How many are there now?
Four, five, six, seven.
Mazel tov!
I just put Jack and
Rose down for their nap.
And I'm trying to keep the more
attractive ones in this area.
This is a nightmare.
Oh, I caught two of them
trying to eat each other,
so that's something we
need to watch out for.
Look, Bri, that one
looks just like you.
Huh. Well, you know what?
I guess he does.
You know, I was
actually thinking,
this could be a chance for you
to finally make things right.
What? What do you mean?
Well, you do have a son
that you were never there for.
This is your opportunity
to do things differently.
Wow. Maybe you're right.
I suppose I could give it a try.
There you go.
Aw, Dick really
likes you.
I like Dick.
You like Dick!
His name's not Dick,
you idiot. It's Finn.
All right, let's check
our YouTube channel
and see how we're doing.
Boy, they just went right
after Cleveland, didn't they?
Geez, that word looks even
harsher when it's in all caps.
Wow, people really seem to hate
everything we put on here.
That sucks.
And I worked really hard
on taking a picture of myself
every day for a year
and then setting the photos
to an emotional song.
Look.
♪ Hey there, Delilah, what's
it like in New York City? ♪
♪ I'm a thousand miles away ♪
♪ But, girl,
tonight you look so pretty ♪
♪ Yes, you do ♪
♪ Times Square can't shine
as bright as you ♪
♪ I swear it's true ♪
Yeah, so we're, uh, thinking
about selling the house.
Hey, stop squirming in there.
This one's bones all feel loose.
And I think that one is blind.
We'll have
to get him little sunglasses.
Great, because
dog-head/human-ears over here
doesn't react to
anything I say.
Hey! Hey, you!
Okay, this one is deaf.
We are going to be spending
a fortune on schools.
How are we gonna pay for that?
Well, you tell me.
You're the one who insisted
I be a stay-at-home mom.
I don't even have a job.
Well, you better
get one.
And not "writing."
A real job.
Why are you being
such a jerk?
I don't know.
I'm sorry. I just...
I just feel like
once I get them on a schedule,
everything will be fine.
I can't believe we couldn't
come up with a viral video.
We should've just gotten Jimmy
Fallon to do any lame thing.
Coming up, a white waiter
at a Chinese restaurant?
We'll get you the facts
on this bizarre story.
But first,
this week's viral video,
"Fat Kid Hustles
Through Crosswalk."
Here it is. Here's little
Chubbo pulling up the rear.
Oh, he's got to get moving now.
That's right. Don't let your
chocolate levels get too low.
I can't believe
Chris gets four million hits
just crossing the street.
I guess we were
trying too hard.
Hey, I went by your house
the other day.
Is your baby pregnant?
I don't know. Lois is
in charge of the kids.
Stewie, this is awful.
I don't know why anyone
would want to be a parent,
especially
to four children.
Four? I thought
we were down to five.
Yeah, the deaf one
didn't hear Joe's lawnmower.
Oh. That's really upsetting.
I-I can't take this
anymore, Stewie.
I-I'm sorry. I got
to get out of here.
What? Where are you going?
Stop doing that!
I need a break,
all right?
I-I j... I just got
to get away for a couple weeks.
A couple weeks?
Y-You're not leaving me
alone with these things.
The whole point of this was for
us to spend more time together.
Wait, what are you talking
about? The whole point of what?
Well, you've been so distant
lately.
I thought if we had a baby it
would bring us closer together.
What? I was only distant
because you've been so moody
lately.
I thought you needed more space.
I always want
to hang out with you.
Well, I was only moody
because you were so distant!
I always want
to hang out with you, too!
Oh, my God.
So we didn't have
to do any of this.
I-I guess not.
How attached to them are you?
Not at all.
Yeah, me either.
This is for the best.
Yeah, I mean, I'm sure
they'll be adopted.
Oh, God, yeah.
I'm still keeping all the gifts
from the baby shower.
You had a baby shower?
Oh!
Now this makes it real!
Oh, my goodness. That's enough
cake for you, Mary Beth.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru